Inventory of the Sheldon H. Harris Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- "Three Years with the Emperor," by Sigfreid A. Schreiner, 1941-1990. (Box-folder 44: 1)
  Correspondence; an obituary, 1990; rough draft from the author's diary from 1941-1944; and 1 photographic print depicting Sigfreid Schreiner, 1989
- Handwritten notes by Sheldon Harris, undated (Folder 44: 2)
- Writings by Sheldon Harris and others
  - "Black Revolt at San Fernando,", 1969 (Folder 44: 3)
  - "Meanwhile, Back in the Valley,", 1969
  - "A Landmark Decision: L.A.'s Scottsboro Boys Case,", 1970
  - "John Louis O'Sullivan and the Election of 1844,", 1960 (Folder 44: 4)
  - "An American's Impressions of Sierra Leone in 1811,", 1962
  - "John Louis O'Sullivan Serves the Confederacy,", 1964 (Folder 44: 5)
  - "Letters from West Virginia: Management's Version of the 1902 Coal Strike,", 1969
- Miscellany, 2002-2003 (Folder 44: 6)
- Writings by Sheldon Harris and others (Box 45)
  - Paul Cuffe: Black America and the African Return, 1972 (Folder 45: 1)
  - Factories of Death: Japanese Biological Warfare, 1932-1945, and the American Cover-Up, 1994 (Folder 45: 2)
- Unit 731: The Japanese Army's Secret of Secrets, by Peter Williams and David Wallace, 1989 (Folder 45: 3)
- Writings by others in a journal of science and proceedings of a meeting on medical science and compassion, 1988-1992 (Folder 45: 4)
- Factories of Death: Japanese Biological Warfare, 1932-1945, and the American Cover-Up, revised edition (2002), 1999-2002. (Box-folder 46: 1)
  Includes copies translated into Chinese and Japanese, 1999
- Journals containing articles about electronics, environment, dietary supplements, history of black teachers in the south, printed copies of lectures by others, racism, slave trade, sport, and World War II atrocities, 1988-2002 (Folder 46: 2)
- Cards, mostly condolences, and list of names, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 47: 1)
- Obituaries, 2002. (Folder 47: 2-3)
  Announcement of a tribute paid to Sheldon Harris from the City of Los Angeles, clippings, letters of condolence, memoranda, press release, printed matter, and miscellaneous materials relating to his memorial service
- Proliferation: Threat and Response, Office of Secretary of Defense, 1996. (Folder 47: 4)
- Suddenly a Giant: A History of California State University, Northridge, John Broesamle, 1993 (Folder 47: 5)
- Articles, American Historical Review, 1999 (Folder 47: 6)
- Guest book, undated (Folder 47: 7)
- Miscellany, 1994-1999 (Folder 47: 8)
- Sound recordings, 2002, undated.
  "All Things Considered," Dad's Music, and Dad's CD. 3 CD sound discs and 1 compact sound cassette containing Sheldon Harris's interview with National Public Radio, 2002
- 3 photographic prints depicting Sheldon Harris and others, undated (Box-folder 48: 1)
- Miscellany, 2002-2003 and undated. (Folder 48: 2-4)
  Includes a brochure describing atrocities committed by Japanese troops in Unit 731, Harbin camp, China; clippings, greetings card; identification card; messages of condolence; newsletter; photocopy of photographic prints; printed matter; and programs of Sheldon Harris's memorial service
- Videorecordings
  - VHS videocassettes
    - Unit 731, 2000
    - "Odoroki Momonoki 20 Seiki,", undated
    - "Modern History-Documentary of the Unit 731," parts I and II, 1992
- Nobody Knows: The Inside Scoop on Capital Punishment, Shoji Kondo, undated. (Box-folder 49: 1)
  Rough translation of original title
- Earth's Cry: 82 Years of Life for Anti-War and Peace, Takemitsu Ogawa, 1995
- Massacre and Resistance, Jin Shenhong, 1999
- Book dealing with Khabarovsk trial and interrogations of Japanese prisoners by a Russian general (prosecutor?), Mitomo Kazuo, undated (Folder 49: 2)
- Diary of Sabuno Endo, 1986
- Testimonies of Japanese war criminals and accounts of eyewitnesses, undated
- Books in Japanese (Folder 49: 3-4)
- Unit 731, 1995 and 1999
- Domestic affairs of the Japanese empire, 1986
- Videorecording--1 VHS videocassette on American disclosure of Japanese army materials, 2000
- Books, pamphlet, and a scrapbook about Unit 731. (Box-folder 50: 1-2)
  Includes materials on biological warfare and international security, 1996-2001 and undated
- Dongbeilunxianshiyanjiu, 1997 (Folder 50: 3)
- Selected archival documents relating to Unit 731--Chemical and biological warfare, undated (Folder 50: 4-6)
- Ronza, 1997 (Box-folder 51: 1)
- Book on exhibits on poison gas in Shinjuli, Tokyo, Japan, 1996 (Folder 51: 2)
- International Symposium on Chinese "Comfort Women,", 2000. (Folder 51: 3)
  Abstract of papers
- Book on Unit 731 criminal acts, 2002 (Folder 51: 4)
- Scrapbook: Photographs reflecting the Japanese Army's massacre at Nanjing, undated (Folder 51: 5)
- Uang Xuan's statement at the Sino-Japanese conference, Nenu, 1998 (Folder 51: 6)
- Shehuikexuezhanxian, 1995 (Folder 51: 7)
- Printed matter on Unit 731 and related materials, 1994-1996, undated (Folder 51: 8)
- Collection of papers presented at the conference on the Sino-Japanese war veterans, Jilein, China, 1995
- Printed matter relating to biological warfare, Japanese occupation of China, and Sino-Japanese relations, undated
- Brochure, undated.
  The Memorial Hall of the Victims in Nanjing Massacre by Japanese invaders
- International Citizen's Forum on War Crimes and Redress, 1999. (Folder 51: 9)
- 1 photographic print depicting Shiro Ishii, 1932
- The Nanking Massacre: Objecting Theories: Thirteen Lies, 1999 (Box 52)
- Books on the history of Japan: Biological and chemical warfare in China and Manchuria; issue of reparation; Japanese atrocities in Jilein province, Beijing; and Sino-Japanese conflict, 1981-2000
- Dai Toa senka gaichi furyo shuyojo, by Chaen Yoshio hen kaisetsu, 1987. (Box-folder 53: 1)
  Photocopy
- Human Radiation Experiments, 1994-1995. (Folder 53: 2)
  Interim and final reports of the advisory committee
- Obituaries, Los Angeles Times, 2002. (Oversize-box 54)
  Includes 6 photographic prints, including 3 depicting Sheldon Harris by himself and 3 depicting him with other unidentified individuals, undated
- Flower ribbons honoring Sheldon Harris, 2002? (Oversize-box 55)